### JOÃO VICTOR FERREIRA PALHA

### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

I have been a fullstack developer for the past 3 years, having experience in both corporate environments and as a freelance professional working on complete projects. Throughout my journey, I have collaborated with a variety of technologies and architectures to ensure optimal performance for my code.

# Portfolio: <a href="https://victor-palha.com">https://victor-palha.com</a> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/Victor-Palha">https://github.com/Victor-Palha</a> Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/joão-palha">www.linkedin.com/in/joão-palha</a>

Blog: <a href="https://victor-palha.github.io/">https://victor-palha.github.io/</a>
Phone: (+55) 091 98970-0567

### **TECHNOLOGIES**

JAVASCRIPT | REACTJS | AWS | NODEJS |
TYPESCRIPT | GIT | SQL | DOCKER | RABBITMQ

#### **EXPERIENCES**

### FREELANCER, BRAZIL FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

**JANUARY DE 2021 - CURRENT** 

## EXECUTIVE SUPERINTENDENT OF URBAN MOBILITY, BRAZIL

**BACKEND DEVELOPER** 

SEPTEMBER DE 2021 - APRIL 2022

### SCIENTIFIC POLICE OF THE STATE OF PARÁ, BRAZIL

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

APRIL DE 2022 - APRIL 2024

### **Coffee Delivery** — Frontend Project (<u>Link</u>)

A web application built in React to create a sleek and interactive design for a fictional coffee delivery store. TypeScript and styled-components were utilized as complementary technologies to enhance the development process.

### **Medieval Tavern** — Fullstack Project (Link)

This API was built in Node.js and Express.js to provide recipes of medieval fantasy food. The API uses the MongoDB database to store the recipes. The API is hosted on Render for free. The front end was made on React.js and with Tailwind

#### **EDUCATION**

CONTACT

### Faci Wyden College (2020 / 2024)

Computer Science degree.

### Rocketseat (2023 / 2024)

Specialization in the JavaScript ecosystem, both in front-end and back-end development.

### MBA Rocketseat (2024 / Current)

MBA in Full-Stack Development Specialization

### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese English